<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

  <string name="idesc_40mm">High Explosive 40mm grenade with a small blast radius for engaging grouped infantry and light vehicles.</string>
  <string name="idesc_40mm_flash">Flash Bang 40mm grenade with a suppressive flash to temporarily blind enemies in close quarters.</string>
  <string name="idesc_40mm_lvg">Timed 40mm grenade with a small anti-personnel warhead that bounces off surfaces before exploding.</string>
  <string name="idesc_40mm_shg">Flechettes packed in a 40mm cartridge that effectively transforms the launcher into a shotgun.</string>
  <string name="idesc_40mm_smk">40mm grenade that creates a blinding cloud of white smoke on impact which also blocks spotting.</string>
  <string name="idesc_acb90">Battlefield Veteran knife with added gut-hook to take out an enemy in melee and steal their dog tags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_ammo">Stationary persistent Ammo Crate. Soldiers nearby will resupply ammo for all weapons, gadgets, and explosives.</string>
  <string name="idesc_ammo_pack">Single use Ammo Pack that resupplies a small amount of bullets to a single soldier on the move.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bayonett">Standard issue USMC M9 bayonet for melee combat. Use it in melee combat to steal enemy dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_beacon">Portable Spawn Beacon that creates an additional spawn position for a Squad. Only functional as a member of a Squad. When deployed with a clear view of the sky in open environments it will function as a Paradrop Beacon.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bpknife1">Sometimes you need to make your own blade for when things get down and dirty. Utilize this make-shift weapon in melee to steal your enemy\'s dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bpknife2">Traditional Swedish Scout knife in laminated steel. Can be used in the field to steal an enemy\'s dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bpknife3">Modern Trench Knife equipped with a knuckle duster style hand guard for stealing enemy dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bpknife4">Lightweight and quiet, use this sleek knife in melee combat to steal dog tags from your opponent.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bpknife5">Handy blade to have out in the battlefield. Use it in melee combat to steal the dogtags of your enemy.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bpknife6">A well-known fighting knife with a long blade sharpened on both sides near the tip. Use it to steal an opponent\'s dog tags, and clean the carcass afterwards.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bpknife7">A short dagger carried inside a boot or strapped to a leg. This backup blade comes in handy opening a stubborn ration pack or relieving an enemy of his dog tags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_bpknife8">This knife has passed one of the most rigorous evaluation programs in the world. It can be relied upon to swiftly and cleanly steal enemy dog tags while retaining its razor sharp edge.</string>
  <string name="idesc_c4">Plastic explosives that stick to most surfaces. Capable of a Mobility Kill on vehicles, and the remote detonator allows for traps and ambushes.</string>
  <string name="idesc_claymore">Anti-personnel mine that launches 3 trip wires shortly after being deployed. Breaking a wire will detonate the mine. A mine with no trip wires is unable to detonate and should be redeployed.</string>
  <string name="idesc_defib">Automated External Defibrillator (AED) revives downed teammates and electrocutes enemies. Charging the paddles will revive teammates with increased health. Needs to recharge after multiple quick uses.</string>
  <string name="idesc_diverknife">Crafted to withstand the harshness of the deep sea. An indispensable tool in any diver\'s kit. Use it in melee combat to steal your enemy\'s dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_dmrs">Unlocks the RFB and Designated Marksman Rifles (DMRs) for All Kits. Â Use the RFB to unlock additional Designated Marksman Rifles.</string>
  <string name="idesc_eod">Remote-controlled Explosive Ordnance Disposal which can repair friendly vehicles, sabotage enemy assets, disarm explosives, and arm or disarm Rush objectives.</string>
  <string name="idesc_fgm148">Guided Anti-Tank missile launcher that locks on to land vehicles. Warhead does medium damage to armor from any angle of attack. Launcher must maintain lock until the missile hits the target.</string>
  <string name="idesc_fim92">Fire and Forget Anti-Air missile capable of Mobility Kills on most aircraft at short range. STINGER missiles will guide themselves to the target after launch.</string>
  <string name="idesc_first_aid_pack">Single use Medic Pack that slowly heals a single soldier to full health, even on the move. Any damage will cancel the heal.</string>
  <string name="idesc_flare">Emergency Red Flare which burns to light up dark space and provides a small blinding effect.</string>
  <string name="idesc_flashbang">Hand grenade with a suppressive Flash Bang effect to temporarily blind enemies in close quarters.</string>
  <string name="idesc_igla">Anti-Air missile capable of Mobility Kills on most aircraft at medium range. Launcher must maintain lock until the missile hits the target.</string>
  <string name="idesc_impact">Russian RGO Impact grenade which explodes shortly after impacting a surface. A smaller grenade with a lower blast yield, two of these grenades can be carried at one time.</string>
  <string name="idesc_knife14100bt">The recurve design of this blade extends its cutting edge and adds extra bite when slicing through objects or stealing an enemy\'s dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_knife2142">A knife designed for the battlefields of the future. That doesn\'t mean you have to wait to get your hands on it. Use it to steal your enemy\'s dogtags today!</string>
  <string name="idesc_knifeprecision">Machined from a single piece of steel, this lightweight dagger is a solid choice for stealing your enemy\'s dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m136">Confined Space version of the M136, capable of being fired indoors without harming the shooter.  A capable dumb fire anti-armor and anti-personnel weapon.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m15">High Explosive Anti-Tank mine that detonates when vehicles pass by in close proximity. Capable of a Mobility Kill on even the heaviest armored vehicles.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m18">Timed fuze hand thrown grenade that creates a blinding cloud of Smoke which also blocks spotting.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m2">Selectable Lightweight Attack Munition usable as either an off-route Anti-Tank mine or a traditional land mine. Blast damage is less than the M15, but is still capable of a Mobility Critical on heavily armored vehicles.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m26_flechette">Compact shotgun capable of being mounted below the barrel of some Assault Rifles. Loaded with flechette rounds which reduce damage but increase range and penetration.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m26_frag">Compact shotgun capable of being mounted below the barrel of some Assault Rifles. Loaded with explosive FRAG ammunition for increased suppressing power.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m26_mass">Compact shotgun capable of being mounted below the barrel of some Assault Rifles. Loaded with standard buckshot with high damage but no penetration.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m26_slug">Compact shotgun capable of being mounted below the barrel of some Assault Rifles. Loaded with SABOT slug rounds for accurate medium range fire.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m32mgl">Fires up to 6 40mm HE grenades before needing to reload. An excellent tool for anti-ambush or heavy assault work.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m34">Incendiary hand grenade which creates a cloud of intense burning particles for a short duration. Particles stick to soldiers and will continue to burn outside the original fire.</string>
  <string name="idesc_m67">Standard timed fuze hand grenade with all around performance and balanced range and damage.</string>
  <string name="idesc_machete">Dima\'s Spetsnaz Machete, take down an enemy with this melee weapon to steal their dog tags as a trophy.</string>
  <string name="idesc_mbtlaw">Smart Anti-Tank missile that automatically detects vehicles near the warhead and guides to the target. Easy to use but low damage from all angles of attack. Capable of locking on to laser-designated targets.</string>
  <string name="idesc_medicbag">Stationary persistent Medic Bag. Soldiers nearby will slowly heal to full health even in combat.</string>
  <string name="idesc_mortar">Remote-controlled 60mm Mortar that fires high explosive rounds using a terrain grid targeting system. Shells travel a ballistic path and may hit objects between the launcher and the intended target. Rapid fire is very inaccurate, single shells have great precision.</string>
  <string name="idesc_motion_sensor">Thrown Motion Sensor which detects enemy movement in 25m radius and reports it to your team\'s minimap for up to 24 seconds after deployment.</string>
  <string name="idesc_mpaps">Man-Portable Active Protection System that detonates incoming explosive Rockets and Shells from both infantry and vehicles before they can hit their targets. Will not stop normal bullets or hand thrown grenades. Can destroy multiple incoming threats in a 180-degree arc, but must recharge between uses.</string>
  <string name="idesc_pld">Portable Laser Designator that laser paints targets while lock is maintained. The designator enables friendlies with missile systems to lock on to the targeted vehicles.</string>
  <string name="idesc_repair">Hand held oxy-fuel welding and cutting torch that repairs friendly vehicles and damages enemy vehicles and infantry.</string>
  <string name="idesc_rpg7">Powerful rocket-propelled Anti-Vehicle launcher capable of disabling even heavily armored vehicles from the sides and rear.</string>
  <string name="idesc_shank">Improvised prison melee weapon to take down enemies in close quarters and steal their dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_shotguns">Unlocks the QBS-09 and Shotguns for All Kits.  Use the QBS-09 to unlock additional Shotguns.</string>
  <string name="idesc_smaw">High speed, low drag Anti-Vehicle launcher with flatter trajectory but lower damage than the RPG-7V2. Most effective against the sides and rear of armored targets.</string>
  <string name="idesc_soflam">Special Operations Forces Laser Marker that automatically laser-paints enemy vehicles when deployed in a stationary position. Capable of remote operation, the SOFLAM enables friendlies with missile systems to lock on to the targeted vehicles.</string>
  <string name="idesc_sraw">The Wire-Guided Anti-Tank missile launcher can be manually guided to the target as long as the launcher is in aimed mode. Capable of locking on to laser-designated targets.</string>
  <string name="idesc_starstreak">Fires a cluster of 3 projectiles that are highly effective against both Aircraft and Light Vehicles. Launcher must maintain lock until the missile hits the target. Capable of locking on to laser designated targets.</string>
  <string name="idesc_ugs">Tactical Unattended Ground Sensor which detects enemy movement in 25m radius and reports it to your team\'s minimap.</string>
  <string name="idesc_v40">Mini hand grenade that can be thrown further than the standard M67 but with reduced blast yield. 3 of these grenades can be carried.</string>
  <string name="idesc_xm25">Fires 25mm grenades that can explode mid-flight creating an airburst effect to eliminate targets behind cover. Aiming down the sights at a cover will lock in that distance, allowing the grenade to explode in the air 3 meters past the cover.</string>
  <string name="idesc_xm25_flechette">Fires a 25mm cartridge packed with penetrating Flechettes that effectively transform the launcher into a semiautomatic shotgun.</string>
  <string name="idesc_xm25_smk">Fires 25mm grenades that can explode mid-flight creating an airburst smoke effect to block sight and spotting. Aiming down the sights at a cover will lock in that distance, allowing the grenade to explode in the air 3 meters past the cover.</string>
  <string name="xp2_idesc_40mm_3gl">Fires 3 smaller 40mm grenades for attacking several targets with less damage than the HE grenade.</string>
  <string name="xp2_idesc_aamine">Anti-Air Mine which targets air vehicles flying within its radius.</string>
  <string name="idesc_neck">A small knife usually carried in a sheath worn around the neck on a breakaway chain. Readily available and easy to deploy, use it to steal your enemy\'s dogtags.</string>
  <string name="idesc_shield">A heavy ballistic shield that will easily stop most small projectiles. The viewport, however, is vulnerable to heavy rounds such us shotgun slugs, sniper fire and explosives.</string>
</resources>